<layout>
  <panel name="body" index="1" height="1734">
    <component cid="textbox" x="23" y="158" w="583" h="1363" responsive="px,fs,px,,tl,23,158,82.420740;347;23;38,13,,309|px,fs,px,,tl,23,132,90.527950;644;23;38,24,,606|px,fs,px,,tl,27,83,95.080320;996;27;22,9,,974|px,px,px,,tc;-14,11,91,991,18,,320|" intelc=",6nt,29f,29f," itemId="735" design=""><![CDATA[After purchasing a subscription to host your web site on the Rennder platform, you will be able to set up two of your own domain names for your web site. Rennder does not sell domain names, so you will be required to purchase one from any of the various domain name registrars on the internet, such as the ones below:<br /><br />
<ul>
<li><a href="http://www.1and1.com" target="_blank">1and1.com</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.register.com" target="_blank">register.com</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.domain.com" target="_blank">domain.com</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.godaddy.com" target="_blank">godaddy.com</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.domainnames.com" target="_blank">domainnames.com</a></li>
</ul>
<h3 style="padding-bottom: 12px;">&nbsp;</h3>
<h3 style="padding-bottom: 12px;">Step #1 : Build your web site</h3>
<div style="padding-bottom: 12px;">Before setting up your domain name to work with the Rennder platform, you should log into your web site from the rennder.com sub-domain you chose (myname.rennder.com), and build your entire web site. Share the link with friends &amp; colleagues to make sure that your web site looks professional, is complete, and contains no mis-spelled words or controversial imagery.</div>
<h3 style="padding-bottom: 12px;">&nbsp;</h3>
<h3 style="padding-bottom: 12px;">Step #2 : Set up Name Servers</h3>
<div style="padding-bottom: 12px;">Once you are ready to point your domain name to your Rennder web site, log into your domain name registrar account from the web site you purchased your domain name from. Find the page to manage your domain name settings, and change the name servers for your domain name to <strong>ns1.rennder.com</strong>, <strong>ns2.rennder.com</strong>, <strong>ns3.rennder.com</strong>, &amp; <strong>ns4.rennder.com</strong>.</div>
<h3 style="padding-bottom: 12px;">&nbsp;</h3>
<h3 style="padding-bottom: 12px;">Step #3: Add domain name to your web site</h3>
<div style="padding-bottom: 12px;">Log into your Rennder web site and go to the settings section within your dashboard, and check to make sure that your domain name is listed within your settings. If not, click the link "Add a Domain Name", and simply type in the domain name you want to use, without including "http://www." (e.g. mydomain.com).</div>
<h3 style="padding-bottom: 12px;">&nbsp;</h3>
<h3 style="padding-bottom: 12px;">Step #4: Be patient!</h3>
<div style="padding-bottom: 12px;">Changing name servers may take a few hours, and can take up to 48 hours in some cases. Within a few hours, start checking to see if your web site is live by typing in the domain name in your favorite web browser (Chrome or Firefox). If your web site loads, your web site is officially live! Congratulations!</div>
<h3 style="padding-bottom: 12px;">&nbsp;</h3>
<h3 style="padding-bottom: 12px;">Step #5: Enabling Email</h3>
<div style="padding-bottom: 12px;">Rennder does not support email services, so you must use your own email server if you want to send &amp; receive emails from your domain name. There are quite a few reliable email services on the internet that support custom domain names, such as the ones below:<br /><br />
<ul>
<li>fastmail.fm</li>
<li>mail.com</li>
<li>gmail.com</li>
<li>hotmail.com</li>
<li>yahoo.com</li>
</ul>
<div style="padding-bottom: 12px;">After you have set up an account with your favorite email service provider, or have set up your own hosted email server, log into your web site and go to the settings section within your dashboard. Click the "edit" link next to your domain name, and change the mail settings IP address and MX record. You can keep the MX record the same (mail.yourdomain.com) if your email server only needs an IP address, but if your email service provider requires your MX record to point to their sub-domain, then you must change it accordingly.</div>
</div>]]></component>
    <component cid="textbox" x="21" y="69" w="328px" h="32px" responsive="px,fs,px,,tl,21,69,83.861670;347;21;35,0,,312|px,px,px,,tl,23,70,341,-4,,364|px,px,px,,tr,-1325,26,371,20,,-42|px,px,px,,tc;336,11,34,328,20,,1076|" intelc="29f,,,," itemId="6nt" design=""><![CDATA[<h3>Setting up your Domain Names</h3>]]></component>
  </panel>
  <layers>
    <layer id="104" name="Header Dashboard" />
    <layer id="153" name="Foot" />
    <layer id="659" name="Support Header" />
  </layers>
  <CSS><![CDATA[]]></CSS>
</layout>