<layout>
  <panel name="body" index="1" height="620">
    <component cid="textbox" x="11" y="572" w="300px" h="100px" responsive="px,px,px,,tl,12,572,300,14,,312|px,px,px,,tl,16,330,300,17,,316|px,px,px,,tl,18,118,300,8,,318|px,px,px,,tc;-351,11,118,300,8,,491|" intelc="y2r,y2r,3d3,3d3," index="9" itemId="g06" design="" frames=""><![CDATA[<h2>What is RML?</h2>]]></component>
    <component cid="textbox" x="11" y="173" w="370px" h="786px" responsive="px,fs,px,,tl,13,627,87.234040;329;13;29,8,,300|px,fs,px,,tl,19,378,91.205210;614;19;35,-2,,579|px,fs,px,,tl,20,170,76.200200;979;20;213,2,,766|px,px,px,,tc;-106,11,173,786,5,,507|" intelc="g06,g06,g06,g06," index="10" itemId="6yg" design="" frames=""><![CDATA[<div style="padding-bottom: 12px;">The Rennder Markup Language (RML) is similar to HTML or XML, and is used to provide <strong>skinnable content</strong> for <a href="#r=Support Components">Components</a>.&nbsp; There are 10+ different RML files, and each one is used for a different type of content, such as a menu system, blog entry, and even a simple button or textbox. Each RML file can contain many unique designs to choose from, and users can select which design to use when configuring components on their web pages.</div>
<h4>Development</h4>
<div style="padding-bottom: 12px;">The beauty about RML is that you don't have to write your markup from scratch. Every web site on the Rennder platform includes a set of RML designs to choose from, so if you do decide to create a custom design of your own, all you need to do is copy &amp; paste the source code of one design and modify it within the built-in <a href="#r=Support-Source-Code-Editor">source code editor</a> located in your web site dashboard. You can find documentation for every RML file on the right-hand side of this page as well.<br /><br />RML is a server-side markup language, so when a web page is loaded in the web browser, all RML tags are removed via the server-side and HTML is served in its place. There are designated areas within an RML design where you can include HTML &amp; CSS code. In the documentation, you'll find that these places are marked like so: <span class="code code-comment">(add html design here)</span>. Adding HTML &amp; CSS to these areas is crucial to creating a custom design. The best practice for writing HTML within your RML design is to use CSS classes that are defined within <a href="#r=Support Style CSS">style.css</a>.</div>
<h4 style="text-align: left;">RML Types</h4>
<div style="padding-bottom: 12px;">There are many types of RML tags that have different purposes. Some tags are replaced with HTML data, such as <a href="#r=Support-RML-Type-Value">Value</a>, <a href="#r=Support-RML-Type-Button">Button</a>, or <a href="#r=Support-RML-Type-Object">Object</a> types. Other tags can contain HTML &amp; RML within them, such as <a href="#r=Support-RML-Type-Design">Design</a>, <a href="#r=Support-RML-Type-Item">Item</a>, and <a href="#r=Support RML Type Block">Block </a>types.</div>]]></component>
  </panel>
  <layers>
    <layer id="659" name="Support Header" />
    <layer id="152" name="Support RML Menu" />
    <layer id="919" name="Header" />
  </layers>
  <CSS><![CDATA[]]></CSS>
</layout>