<layout>
  <panel name="body" index="1" height="">
    <component cid="textbox" x="11" y="13" w="1178px" h="989px" responsive="|px,fs,px,,tl,4,13,94.714280;700;4;33,20,,667|px,fs,px,,tl,19,13,57.442110;907;19;367,20,,540|px,px,px,,tc;-10,11,13,989,20,,498|" intelc=",,,," index="1" itemId="1o0" design="" frames=""><![CDATA[<h1>About the Rennder platform</h1>
<br />Rennder is a web development &amp; hosting platform, developed by <a href="http://www.markentingh.com" target="_blank">Mark Entingh</a>, and was launched on May 5th, 2013 after 7+ years of research &amp; development. <br /><br /><br />
<h3>The Mantra</h3>
Rennder is set out to create a more united web where anyone can build their own web application, make money, and live a prosperous life.<br /><br /><br />
<h3>How It Works</h3>
Sign up, select a unique web design template for your new web site, start building web pages within the <a href="#r=Support-Page-Editor">Page Editor</a>, and then publish your web site using your own domain name. It can be done in a single day if you have all of your content ready for your web site. It can be done within a week or less if you don't.<br /><br /><br />
<h3>The Platform</h3>
Every core feature within the Rennder platform is required in order to build a modern web site. This is because the modern web site is a very complex application that requires many different systems to function properly. Rennder is potentially the most advanced CMS platform on the planet because of these core features.<br /><br />
<h5>Components</h5>
Simply drag &amp; drop content directly onto your web pages. A component can have a simple purpose, like text, a photo, a button., and it can be complex as well, such as blog entries, user comments, or a product list. Without components, your pages would have no content.<br /><br />
<h5>Applications</h5>
Install and use complex applications within your web site. So far, Blog Book is the first app available, and there are 6 other applications under development, including e-commerce, scheduling &amp; calendar system, social networking, and forums. Without apps, your web site would be limited to simple content, like text, photos, and videos.<br /><br />
<h5>Responsive Design</h5>
When a web page is displayed in a cell phone or tablet PC, it is most likely unreadable. The text runs off the screen, the photos are too large, and the content is overwhelming for the reader to decode. In my own experience, I could say that 80% of web sites I browse on my own cell phone are difficult to read at best, and this is a major problem for the web as a whole. If a web page that has a responsive design is loaded into a cell phone or tablet PC, photos will shrink, the text will be easier to read, and all the content will stack vertically, making it much easier to browse through.<br /><br />The responsive design system for Rennder is intelligent because all content on a web page can be dragged around freely, and so there is no real structure to the content. There are five screen sizes within a Rennder web page (cell, mobile, tablet, desktop, HD), and your content can be completely rearranged within each of the five screen sizes. Without responsive design, your web pages would not be viewable on any mobile device.<br /><br />Rennder Markup Language (RML)<br /><br /><br />
<h3>The Evolution</h3>
Rennder started out as a small project called <a href="#r=Support-Evolver">Evolver</a>, which I built over a month or so. Evolver was a web page editor, and was very basic compared to Rennder's page editor. I could drag &amp; drop 12+ components onto a web page to create content for a development blog I had started. It eventually turned into a social networking platform, which destracted me from my main focus... the page editor. <br /><br />
<h5>The Platform Begins</h5>
A few years had past, and I had kept the entire project a secret from the online community. Even with a social network built in, I couldn't find a way to get people to use the web site. It simply wasn't ready for the masses. I finally came up with the name "Rennder", bought the domain name, and began redeveloping most of the source code with the goal to make Rennder a first-class web development platform. I wanted something like Adobe Photoshop, and instead of working with layers of artwork, I wanted my users to work with complex applications, photo galleries, buttons, social interations, data lists, and 3rd party widgets. Thus, Rennder Applications was born, and with it came Rennder's first app, Blog Book.<br /><br />
<h5>Rending Itself</h5>
Four years have past since I came up with the idea for Evolver. I had a beautiful interface for Rennder.com which included a social network, web site management dashboard, and a page editor that worked well building simple web pages. I was happy. I was foolish to feel so content, though since Rennder was in it's infancy. At this point in the progress of development, I had started coming up with very game-changing ideas, some of which were given to me by my close friends. Out of these ideas came RML, a thin page editor UI, many server-side technologies, more apps, and something monumental. I transformed the rennder.com web site from being hard-coded and part of the platform, into a web site built using the platform. This was accomplished by converting the old dashboard into components. Basically, Rennder started rendered itself. This was monumental because Rennder had truly become transparent. Users no longer needed to log into rennder.com to manage their web site. They could log into their own web site, and view their own custom designed dashboard.<br /><br />
<h5>The Struggle</h5>
Timewarp three years into the future, 7 years from the beginning. It's 2013 and I find myself with a truly incredible web development platform in my hands, but I lack one important factor. I need web design templates, and I need a lot of them. Right now I have a few, but the time has come for me to take off my developer hat and focus on the eternal beauty of Rennder. I need to give my users a plethera of unique web design templates to choose from. I need to create a masterpiece out of Rennder. Most of all, I need to set good standards for web design in general. This is my journey now. I plan to change the web site&nbsp;forever&nbsp;for everyone.<br /><br /><br />Below is a gallery of screen shots taken of Rennder before 2010. Most of which were taken of the old dashboard before the web site was discarded and the dashboard converted into a component.]]></component>
    <component cid="photogallery" x="236" y="1253" w="470px" h="300px" responsive="px,px,px,,tc;164,11,1287,670,7,,169|px,px,px,,tc;-11,11,677,670,39,,169|px,px,px,,tr,-1370,11,330,39,,26|px,px,px,,tl,236,1253,970,62,,1206|" intelc="1o0,1o0,1o0,1o0," index="2" itemId="9mh" design="grid|6|20|med|150|1|0||||Previous|More Photos" frames=""><![CDATA[elsvhqvuvx.jpg||alyjeuujue.jpg||txicraaoag.jpg||xxwssdwxms.jpg||amsnltnkfm.jpg||fbxmtveboj.jpg||stpqpmwvgg.jpg||cuyqcolrqi.jpg||jdypwighlw.jpg||gwmiopfsbk.jpg||eiohijagwr.jpg||rgtpbfaqup.jpg||rhceeirqfe.jpg||dpciebkrny.jpg||lpyuhauwry.jpg||wsthjavpft.jpg||ufmkeiyame.jpg||fujchirqik.jpg||xsawhkvvbn.jpg||rafduaqvty.jpg||ygplsmname.jpg||ujbfgwhxqc.jpg||snjqylywoh.jpg||vtjndmumsv.jpg||nvuxwlxeue.jpg||knvtljkwaj.jpg||jqeoqeykuv.jpg||edxxooytha.jpg||qxlrtqbrmh.jpg||xfrtprxbyi.jpg||quwsfkoshy.jpg||maoliqlotd.jpg||ubvhwbwwer.jpg||rtxiuojtha.jpg||tediikdpyi.jpg|]]></component>
  </panel>
  <layers>
    <layer id="104" name="Header Dashboard" />
  </layers>
  <CSS><![CDATA[]]></CSS>
</layout>